Guide to the Yale School of Drama Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Drama School, 1966-1983; Accession 1986-A-026
  - Yale Rep Plays
    - Playwright's Project, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 279)
    - "Puntila", 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 280 - 281)
    - "Reunion"/ "Dark Pony", 1977 (Box 17, Folder 282)
    - "The Durango Flash", 1977 (Box 17, Folder 283)
    - "The Ghost Sonata", 1977 (Box 17, Folder 284)
    - House Manager's Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 285)
    - Press Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 17, Folder 286)
    - Rehearsal and Production Schedule, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 287)
    - "Sganarelle: An Evening of Moliere Farces", 1977 (Box 18, Folder 288)
    - Stage Manager's Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 289)
    - "The 1940's Radio Hour", 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 290)
    - Notes Regarding "Underground," Never Produced, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 291)
    - Program Advertising, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 292)
    - Reviews, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 293)
    - "Jack, or the Submission" (workshop), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 294)
    - "Mad Dog Blues" (Workshop 1), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 295)
    - "Mahagunny", 1978 (Box 18, Folder 296)
    - Student Reps 1 and 2, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 297)
    - "The Wild Duck", 1978 (Box 19, Folder 298)
    - "The Winter's Tale", 1978 (Box 19, Folder 299)
    - "Farewell to Jacques Brel", 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 300)
    - House Manager's Report, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 301)
    - "Mistaken Identities": "Guesswork" and "Dentity Crisis", 1978 (Box 19, Folder 302)
    - Rehearsal Schedule, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 303)
    - "Tales from the Vienna Woods", 1978 (Box 19, Folder 304)
    - "The Bundle", 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 305)
    - "Buried Child'', 1979 (Box 19, Folder 306)
    - "The Seagull", 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 307)
    - "Wings", 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 308)
      - Boston Royalties, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 309)
      - New York Royalties, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 310)
      - Washington Royalties, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 311)
    - "Curse of the Starving Class", 1978-1980 (Box 20, Folder 312)
    - House Manager's Report, 1978-1980 (Box 20, Folder 313)
    - "Family Rites", 1979 (Box 20, Folder 314)
    - "Wings: London Royalties, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 315)
    - "Yerma", 1979 (Box 20, Folder 316)
    - "A Lesson from Aloes" (New York), 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 317)
    - "Agammemnon", 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 318)
    - As You Like It, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 319)
    - "Bosoms and Neglect", 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 320)
    - Box Office, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 321)
    - Drums in the Night, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 322)
    - "Kasimir and Karoline", 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 323)
    - "Measure for Measure", 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 324)
    - Agreement (Playwright), 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 325)
    - Drama School Productions, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 326)
    - Rehearsal Schedule, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 327)
    - Season, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 328)
    - "The Idiot", 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 329)
    - "They're Dying Out", 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 330)
    - "Timon of Athens'', 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 331)
    - "Ubu Rex'', 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 332)
    - Casting, 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 333)
    - Memos, 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 334)
    - Press Notices, 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 335)
    - Press Releases, 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 336)
    - Press Director, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 337)
    - Public Relations, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 338)
    - Reviews, 1979-1983 (Box 22, Folder 339)
    - "A Play by Giants", 1980 (Box 22, Folder 340)
    - "Boesman and Lena", 1980 (Box 22, Folder 341)
    - "Jungle of Cities", 1980 (Box 22, Folder 342)
    - "La Sagouine", 1980 (Box 22, Folder 343)
    - "Mutiny in Silence After a Last Sniper", 1980 (Box 23, Folder 344)
    - "Ophelia Kline", 1980 (Box 23, Folder 345)
    - "The Bakkhai", 1980 (Box 23, Folder 346)
    - "Twelfth Night", 1980 (Box 23, Folder 347)
    - Box Office, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 348)
    - "An Attempt at Flying", 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 349 - 350)
      - Correspondence, Background, Review, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 351)
      - Notes, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 352)
    - Daily Stage Manager's Report, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 353)
    - "Domestic Issues", 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 354)
    - House Manager 's Report, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 355)
    - "Lady Lester", 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 356)
    - Productions, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 357)
    - Publicity, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 358)
    - Rehearsal Schedule, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 359)
    - "Rococo", 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 360)
    - "Sally and Marsha", 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 361)
    - Season, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 362)
    - "The Talisman", 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 363)
    - Managing Directors, 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 364)
    - Managing Directors, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 365)
    - Winterfest, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 366)
      - Miscellaneous, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 367)
      - Reviews, Publicity and Notes, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 368)
      - Script Requests, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 369)
    - "Hedda Gabler", 1981 (Box 25, Folder 370)
    - "Mrs. Warren's Profession", 1981 (Box 25, Folder 371)
      - Casting, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 372)
      - Reviews and Correspondence, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 373)
    - "No Limits to Love", 1981 (Box 25, Folder 374)
    - "Plenty", 1981 (Box 25, Folder 375)
    - "The Magnificent Cuckold", 1981 (Box 25, Folder 376)
    - "Uncle Vanya", 1981 (Box 25, Folder 377)
      - Casting, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 378)
      - Reviews, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 379)
    - Box Office, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 380)
    - Contact Sheets, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 381)
    - "Flashfloods"/Winterfest, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 382 - 383)
    - "Going Over"/Winterfest, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 384 - 385)
    - Literary Managers, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 386)
    - News Releases, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 387)
    - School Productions, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 388)
    - Season, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 389)
    - Publicity, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 390)
    - "Rip Van Winkle", 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 391 - 392)
      - Casting, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 393)
    - Season, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 394)
    - "Sore Throats", 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 395)
    - "The Man Who Could See Through Time"/Winterfest, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 396)
    - "A Doll House", 1982 (Box 26, Folder 397)
      - Casting, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 398)
      - Production Record, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 399)
      - Reviews, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 400)
    - "Beef, No Chicken", 1982 (Box 26, Folder 401)
    - "Coyote Ugly": Rewrites, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 402)
    - "Hello and Goodbye": Reviews, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 403)
    - "High Road, Low Bridge", 1982 (Box 27, Folder 404)
    - "Johnny Bull", 1982 (Box 27, Folder 405)
      - Reviews and Notes, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 406)
    - "Lady Lester", 1982 (Box 27, Folder 407)
    - "Love's Labour Lost": Reviews, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 408)
    - "Master Harold...and the Boys", 1982 (Box 27, Folder 409)
      - Broadway, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 410)
      - Reviews, Notes, Notices, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 411)
    - "One Rule", 1982 (Box 27, Folder 412)
    - "Steaming", 1982 (Box 27, Folder 413)
    - "The Philanderer": Reviews, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 414)
    - Winterfest III, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 415)
    - "Yale Repertory Theater News", 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 416)
    - Press Office, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 417)
    - "A Touch of the Poet", 1983 (Box 28, Folder 418)
    - "About Face", 1983 (Box 28, Folder 419)
    - "Master Barold...and the Boys": South Africa Performance, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 420)
    - "Much Ado About Nothing", 1983 (Box 28, Folder 421)
    - "Playing in Local Bands": Production Notes, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 422)
    - "Donner", undated (Box 28, Folder 423)
    - "Women Beware Women", undated (Box 28, Folder 424)
    - "The Five Kings": Technical Production, undated (Box 28, Folder 425)
    - Printed Programs:, 1973 Fall (Box 29, Folder 426)
      - "The Tempest" (Box 29, Folder 427)
      - "Watergate Classics" (Box 29, Folder 428)
      - "Darkroom" (Box 29, Folder 429)
      - "The Tubs" (Box 29, Folder 430)
      - "The Rise and Fall of the City of Mahagonny", 1974 Spring (Box 29, Folder 431)
      - "Shlemiel the First" (Box 29, Folder 432)
      - "Geography of a Horse Dreamer" (Box 29, Folder 433)
      - "The Frogs" (Box 29, Folder 434)
      - "The Possessed", 1974 Fall (Box 29, Folder 435)
      - "The Idiots Kararnazov" (Box 29, Folder 436)
      - "Victory" (Box 29, Folder 437)
      - "A Midsummer Night's Dream", 1975 Spring (Box 29, Folder 438)
      - "Happy End" (Box 29, Folder 439)
      - "The Shaft of Love" (Box 29, Folder 440)
      - "The Father" (Box 29, Folder 441)
      - "A Midsummer Night's Dream", 1975 Fall (Box 29, Folder 442)
      - "Don Juan" (Box 29, Folder 443)
      - Dynamite Tonight" (Box 29, Folder 444)
      - "Bingo", 1976 Spring (Box 29, Folder 445)
      - "General Gorgeous'' (Box 29, Folder 446)
      - "Troilus and Cressida" (Box 29, Folder 447)
      - "Walk the Dog, Willie" (Box 29, Folder 448)
      - "Ivanov", 1976 Fall (Box 29, Folder 449)
      - "Julius Caesa" (Box 29, Folder 450)
      - "Suicide in B6" (Box 29, Folder 451)
      - "The Vietnamization of New Jersey'', 1977 Spring (Box 29, Folder 452)
      - "The Durango Flash'' (Box 29, Folder 453)
      - "Puntila" (Box 29, Folder 454)
      - "White Marriage" (Box 29, Folder 455)
      - "Reunion"/"Dark Pony", 1977 Fall (Box 29, Folder 456)
      - "The Ghost Sonata" (Box 29, Folder 457)
      - "Sganarelle: An Evening of Moliere Farces", 1978 Spring (Box 29, Folder 458)
      - "Man is Man" (Box 29, Folder 459)
      - "The Wild Duck" (Box 29, Folder 460)
      - "Mahagonny" (Box 29, Folder 461)
      - "Mistaken Identities" (Box 29, Folder 462)
      - "Tales from the Vienna Woods" (Box 29, Folder 463)
      - "Buried Child'', 1979 Spring (Box 29, Folder 464)
      - "As You Like It" (Box 29, Folder 465)
      - "The Bundle" (Box 29, Folder 466)
      - "The Seagull" (Box 29, Folder 467)
      - Miscellaneous, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 468)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 469)
  - Yale Rep - Administrative Records
    - Accident Reports, 1972-1977 (Box 30, Folder 470)
      - 1976-1979 (Box 30, Folder 471)
      - 1979-1981 (Box 30, Folder 472)
    - Addresses, Telephone Numbers, and Miscellaneous Information (Faculty and Students)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 473)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 474)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 475)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 476)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 477)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 478)
    - Affirmative Action, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 479)
    - Alterations: Physical Plant
      - 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 480 - 481)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 482)
      - 1973-1976 (Box 30, Folder 483 - 484)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 485)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 486)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 487)
    - American Broadcasting Company (ABC), 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 488)
    - American Dance Festival, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 489)
    - American Theatre Association: Convention Material, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 490)
      - Convention, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 491)
    - Dean's Annual Report (Box 31, Folder 492)
    - Arts Council of Greater New Haven, 1972-1975 (Box 31, Folder 493)
    - Associates of Yale Theatre, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 494)
    - Audit Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 495)
      - 1976 (Box 31, Folder 496)
    - Authorized Departmental Signatures, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 497)
    - Bank, Use of
      - 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 498)
      - 1979-1981 (Box 31, Folder 499)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 500)
    - Box Office Receipts and Analyses, 1968-1978 (Box 31, Folder 501)
    - Actors' Support Budget
      - 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 502)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 503)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 504)
    - Actors' Support and Professional Fees Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 505)
    - Fall Brochure Estimate, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 506)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1974-1976 (Box 32, Folder 507 - 508)
    - Budget: Production Expenses (Box 32, Folder 509)
    - Budgets: Miscellaneous
      - 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 510)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 511)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 512)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 513)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 514)
    - Production Budgets, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 515)
    - Proposed Budget, 1974-1975, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 516)
    - Drama School, Yale Repertory Theatre: Budgets and Proposed Chart of Accounts Change, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 517)
    - Budget Support, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 518)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 519)
    - Theatre Budget: Memos, Correspondence, Worksheets, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 520)
    - Business Machine Forms, 1971-1974 (Box 33, Folder 521)
    - Cable Television: New Haven, undated (Box 33, Folder 522)
    - Calvary Baptist Church, 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 523)
    - Calvin Hill Day Care Center, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 524)
    - Campaign for Yale, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 525)
    - CBS Fellows, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 527)
    - Chart of Accounts, 1972-1974 (Box 33, Folder 528)
    - Cigarette License, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 529)
    - Community Relations, 1979-1981 (Box 33, Folder 531)
      - 1981 (Box 33, Folder 532)
    - Company Housing
      - 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 533)
      - 1974-1977 (Box 33, Folder 534)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 535)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 536)
    - Computer Center Matters, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 537)
    - Computer Matters, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 538)
    - Connecticut Advocates for the Arts, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 539)
    - Connecticut Commission on the Arts, 1973-1977 (Box 34, Folder 540 - 541)
      - Grants, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 542)
    - Contributions, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 543)
    - Correspondence, Summer, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 544)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 545)
      - 1979-1983 (Box 34, Folder 546)
      - Managing Director's, 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 547)
    - Giamatti, A. Bartlett, 1979-1980 (Box 35, Folder 549)
    - Gymnasium: Form Letters, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 551)
      - Use of, 1979-1981 (Box 35, Folder 552)
      - 1981 (Box 35, Folder 553)
    - Holiday Inn: Form Letters, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 554)
    - Housing, 1979-1981 (Box 35, Folder 555)
    - Keys to Theater, 1977-1979 (Box 35, Folder 556)
    - League of Resident Theatres, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 557)
    - Library: Form Letters, 1977-1979 (Box 35, Folder 559)
      - Use of, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 560)
      - 1981 (Box 35, Folder 561)
    - Liquor Permit, 1969-1978 (Box 35, Folder 562)
    - Mailing Permit: Bridgeport, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 563)
      - Bulk, 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 564)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 566)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), 1972 (Box 35, Folder 567)
    - Opportunity Resources, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 568)
    - Potential Directors, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 570 - 571)
    - Potential Designers, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 572)
    - Producers Group International, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 573)
    - Publicity, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 574)
    - Publicity, 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 575)
      - 1979-1982 (Box 36, Folder 576)
    - Radio Theatre Proposal, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 577)
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1980-1982 (Box 36, Folder 579)
    - Subscriber Extended Renewal, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 580)
    - Subscription Campaign, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 581)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 582)
    - Subscription Letter, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 583)
    - Technical Design and Production, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 584)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 585)
    - Theatre Sound, 1967-1970 (Box 36, Folder 586)
    - Theatre Techniques, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 587)
    - Unit Set, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 588)
  - Correspondence (Dept, Theatre, School)
    - A Correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 37, Folder 589)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 590)
    - Actors' Equity Association: Miscellaneous, 1973-1977 (Box 37, Folder 591)
    - Advocates for the Arts, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 593)
    - American Arts Alliance, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 594)
      - 1979-1981 (Box 37, Folder 595)
      - 1982 (Box 37, Folder 596)
    - American Dance Festival, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 597)
    - American Repertory Theatre Company, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 598)
    - Arts Council of Greater New Haven, 1970-1972 (Box 37, Folder 599)
      - 1979-1982 (Box 37, Folder 600)
    - Associated Councils for the Arts, undated (Box 38, Folder 601)
    - Association of Arts Administration Educators, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 602)
    - Atlantic Theatre Company, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 603)
    - B Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 604)
      - 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 605)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 38, Folder 606)
    - Bulandra Theatre Company, 1976-1979 (Box 38, Folder 607)
    - C Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 608)
      - 1980 (Box 38, Folder 609)
      - 1982 (Box 38, Folder 610)
    - CBS Cable, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 613)
    - Connecticut Advocates for the Arts, 1977-1979 (Box 38, Folder 614)
      - 1982 (Box 38, Folder 615)
    - The Connecticut Ballet, 1979-1981 (Box 38, Folder 616)
    - Connecticut Commission on the Arts, 1970-1972 (Box 39, Folder 617)
      - 1971-1975 (Box 39, Folder 618)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 39, Folder 619)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 620)
      - 1977 (Box 39, Folder 621)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 622)
    - Connecticut State Scholarships, 1968-1971 (Box 39, Folder 623)
    - Cultural Affairs Study Committee, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 624)
    - D Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 625)
      - 1977-1982 (Box 39, Folder 626)
    - E Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 627)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 628)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 39, Folder 629)
    - Educational Center for the Arts, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 630)
    - Educational Testing Service, 1980-1982 (Box 40, Folder 631)
    - Esslin, Martin, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 633)
    - F Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 634)
      - 1979-1982 (Box 40, Folder 635)
    - Falmouth Playhouse, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 636)
    - G Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 638)
    - G Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 40, Folder 639)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 40, Folder 640)
    - The Guthrie Theatre, 1978-1980 (Box 40, Folder 643)
    - H Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 644)
      - 1972-1981 (Box 40, Folder 645)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 646)
    - Nancy Hanks Memorial, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 648)
    - Hartford Stage Company, 1979-1982 (Box 41, Folder 649)
    - Hartman Theater, 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 650)
    - HBO (Home Box Office), 1982 (Box 41, Folder 651)
    - Historic Landmark Preservation, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 654)
    - Hunter College, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 656)
    - I Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 657)
      - 1978-1982 (Box 41, Folder 658)
    - Ibsen, 1980-1982 (Box 41, Folder 659)
    - Illuminating Engineering Society, 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 660)
    - International Theatre Festival, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 661)
    - International Theatre Institute, 1978-1982 (Box 41, Folder 662)
    - Invitations, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 663)
    - J Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 664)
    - J Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 42, Folder 665)
    - Job Applications: Directing, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 666)
      - Teaching, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 667)
    - Jones, James Earl, 1980-1981 (Box 42, Folder 668)
    - K Correspondence, 1971-1981 (Box 42, Folder 669)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 670)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 42, Folder 671)
    - Kazan, Elia, 1979-1982 (Box 42, Folder 672)
    - Kenyon Festival Theatre, 1982-1983 (Box 42, Folder 673)
    - L Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 675)
      - 1979-1983 (Box 42, Folder 676)
    - League of Professional Theater Training Programs, 1973-1975 (Box 42, Folder 677)
      - 1976-1980 (Box 43, Folder 678)
      - 1980-1983 (Box 43, Folder 679)
    - League of Resident Theatres (LORT), 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 680)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 43, Folder 681)
      - 1979-1982 (Box 43, Folder 682)
      - Actors' Equity Association: Policies, Rules, Agreements, 1971-1976 (Box 43, Folder 683 - 684)
        - Security Agreements and Guarantees, 1972-1976 (Box 43, Folder 685)
      - Mailing Lists and Memberships (Box 43, Folder 686)
      - Minutes from Meetings, 1972-1976 (Box 44, Folder 687)
    - Leonard Davis Center, undated (Box 44, Folder 688)
    - Letters of Recommendation, 1977-1981 (Box 44, Folder 689)
    - Literary Managers: General, 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 690)
    - The Long Wharf Theatre, 1979-1981 (Box 44, Folder 691)
    - M Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box 44, Folder 692)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 693)
      - 1982 (Box 44, Folder 694)
      - 1983 (Box 44, Folder 695)
    - The Macmillan Company, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 696)
    - Unsolicited Manuscripts, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 698)
    - McCarter Theater Contact Sheets, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 699)
    - Algur H. Meadows Award, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 700)
    - N Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 702)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 44, Folder 703)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 705)
      - Observerships, 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 706)
    - National Public Television Memoes, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 707)
    - Nederlander/RKO, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 708)
    - Negro Ensemble, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 709)
    - New Drama Forum Association, 1980-1982 (Box 45, Folder 710)
    - New Haven Civic Ballet, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 711)
    - New Haven Opera Society, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 712)
    - O Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 714)
      - 1979-1983 (Box 45, Folder 715)
    - Ohio State Theatre Programs, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 716)
    - O'Neill Center, 1978-1981 (Box 45, Folder 717)
    - P Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 718)
      - 1980-1983 (Box 45, Folder 719)
    - Press Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 720)
    - Philadelphia Drama Guild, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 721)
    - Pittsburgh Public Theater, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 722)
    - Playbill: Arthur Birsh, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 723)
    - Princeton University: Priority Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 724)
    - Public Broadcasting Service (Various Agreements), 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 725)
    - Q Correspondence, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 726)
    - Q-R Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 727)
    - R Correspondence, 1972-1981 (Box 46, Folder 728)
      - 1982 (Box 46, Folder 729)
      - 1983 (Box 46, Folder 730)
    - Random House, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 731)
    - Rastar Pictures, Inc., 1981 (Box 46, Folder 732)
    - Recommendations, 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 733)
    - Refco Visual Communications, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 734)
    - Resumes, 1970-1971 (Box 46, Folder 735)
    - Lee Rothberg Productions, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 737)
    - S Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 46, Folder 738)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 47, Folder 739)
      - 1982 (Box 47, Folder 740)
      - 1983 (Box 47, Folder 741)
    - Shubert Theatre, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 743)
    - Sirnonides Aid, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 744)
    - Sondheim, Stephen, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 745)
    - Streep, Meryl, 1982-1983 (Box 47, Folder 746)
    - A Survey of Arts Administration Training in U.S. and Canada (Report), 1975 (Box 47, Folder 747)
    - T Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 47, Folder 749)
    - Telephone Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 750)